A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 10 FA1318
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio Recordings, 1967-2004; 1; All items are 1/4 inch audio tape unless otherwise noted.
  - Conferences, Seminars, Lectures, and Meetings, 1967-2004; C
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 2 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15537)
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 3 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 85 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15538)
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 4 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 91 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15539)
      Pocantico Conference Center. Tape titled US-China Relations.
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 5 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 91 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15540)
      Pocantico Conference Center. Tape labled US-Taiwan Relations.
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 6 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15541)
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 7 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15542)
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 8 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15543)
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 9 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 83 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15544)
    - Zhu Rongji Address, 2001 October 2; 12 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15545)
      Tape 1 of 1.
      Congratulatory message on the NCUSCR's 35th anniversary. The six-minute address is recorded twice.
    - Ralph Cossa Conversation with John Holden, 2001 November 6; 48 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15546)
      John Holden telephone interview with Ralph Cossa.
      Tape labeled "Sara[h] Bush - National Committee on US-China Relations - Tape 1 of 1." Sarah Bush was the call organizer.
    - Zhou Mingwei Talk, 2002 January 14?; 45 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15597)
      Talk on Taiwan and cross-strait relations, followed by questions. Occasion not identified.
      Tape labeled "Zhou Mingwei, tape 1 of 1."
    - Annual Members Luncheon - Richard Haass Address - Tape 1, 2002 December 5; 48 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15560A)
      Ambassador Haass, director of Policy Planning at the U.S. State Department, spoke on China and the Future of U.S. - China relations.
    - Annual Members Program - Richard Haass Q & A and Panel Discussion - Tape 2, 2002 December 5; 46 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15561A)
      Richard Haass Q & A (continued); off-the-record Panel presentations by Charles Conway and John Holden for Thomas Christensen. (Continued on AV 15560B.)
    - Annual Members Program - Panel Discussion - Tape 3, 2002 December 5; 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15560B)
      Off-the-record Panel presentations by David M. Lampton, John Kamm, Jamie Horseley, and James Sasser.
    - Annual Members Program - Panel Discussion Q & A - Tape 4, 2002 December 5; 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15561B)
    - Annual Members Program - Panel Discussion Q & A - Tape 5, 2002 December 5; 11 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15562A)
    - SARS Conference - Tape 1 of 2, 2003 June 18; 125 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15563)
      Conference held at the New York Life Insurance offices in New York. Panels on the Political and International Impact of SARS, and on the Impact of SARS on the Media.
    - SARS Conference - Tape 2 of 2, 2003 June 18; 125 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15564)
      Panel on the Economic Impact of the SARS outbreak; Address by Laurie Garrett (science journalist, with focus on emerging diseases).
    - SARS Conference - Part 1, 2003 June 18; 61 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15565A)
    - SARS Conference - Part 2, 2003 June 18; 61 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15565B)
    - SARS Conference - Part 3, 2003 June 18; 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15566A)
    - SARS Conference - Part 4, 2003 June 18; 61 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15566B)
    - SARS Conference - Part 5, 2003 June 18; 12 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15567)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 1 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15568)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 2 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15569)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 3 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 65 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15570)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 4 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15571)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 5 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15572)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 6 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 23 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15573)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 7 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15574)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 8 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15575)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 9 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15576)
    - New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 10 of 10, 2003 August 8-10; 66 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15577)
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, Annual Meeting - Tape 1 of 3, 2004 November 10; 92 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15578)
      Thirty-eighth annual meeting. Business meeting, panel of speakers (Kenneth Lieberthal, Chung Lee, and David Malpass), and question and answer period.
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, Annual Meeting - Tape 2 of 3, 2004 November 10; 16 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15579)
      Thirty-eighth annual meeting. Conclusion of Q & A addressed to panel of speakers (Kenneth Lieberthal, Chung Lee, and David Malpass).
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, Annual Meeting - Robert Zoellick Address and Q & A - Tape 3 of 3, Side 1, 2004 November 10; 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15580A)
      Zoellick was the U. S. Trade Representative.
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, Annual Meeting - Robert Zoellick Q & A - Tape 3 of 3, Side 2, 2004 November 10; 17 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15580B)
    - Untitled - Tape 1 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15598)
    - Untitled - Tape 2 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15599)
    - Untitled - Tape 3 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15600)
    - Untitled - Tape 4 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15601)
    - Untitled - Tape 5 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15602)
    - Untitled - Tape 6 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15603)
    - Untitled - Tape 7 of 7, Undated; Sound; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15604)
    - Chinese National Anthem (Chi Lai) and the Star-Spangled Banner, 3 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15428)
  - United States - China Dialogues, 1991-2002; D
    The United States - China Dialogues were initiated in 1984 by the National Committee and the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs, as a way of facilitating frank and productive discussion of sensitive issues between the two countries. Dialogues I-XI (1984-2002) met alternately in the U.S. and China.
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 1, 1991 June 14; 124 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15409)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 2, 1991 June 15; 124 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15410)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 3, 1991 June 15; 126 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15411)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 4, 1991 June 16; 120 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15412)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 5, 1991 June 16; 121 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15413)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 1 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 123 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15429)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 2 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 121 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15430)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 3 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 124 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15431)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 4 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 117 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15432)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 5 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 119 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15433)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 6 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 123 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15434)
    - Fifth United States-China Dialogue, Wingspread Conference Center - Tape 7 of 7, 1991 June 14-17; 117 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15435)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 1 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15414A)
      English-language version of conference recording. This recording captures English-speaking presenters at the conference and simultaneous English-language translations of the remarks of Chinese-speaking presenters.
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 1 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15414B)
      Chinese-language version of conference recording. This recording captures Chinese-speaking presenters at the conference and simultaneous Chinese-language translations of the remarks of English-speaking presenters.
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 2 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15415A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 2 of 12, 1993 April 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 62 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15415B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 3 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15416A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 3 of 12, 1993 April 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 63 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 15416B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 4 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15417A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 4 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15417B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 5 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15418A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 5 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15418B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 6 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15419A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 6 of 12, 1993 April 1; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15419B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 7 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15420A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 7 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15420B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 8 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15421A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 8 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15421B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 9 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15422A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 9 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15422B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 10 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15423A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 10 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15423B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 11 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15424A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 11 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15424B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 12 of 12, 1993 April 3; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15425A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 12 of 12, 1993 April 2; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15425B)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 13, 1993 April 3; Sound, 50 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15426A)
    - Sixth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 13, 1993 April 3; Sound, 50 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15426B)
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session One - Tape 1 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 85 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15436)
      Session chair, Ambassador Liu Shuqing.
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session One - Tape 2 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 75 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15437)
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Two - Tape 3 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 67 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15438)
      Session chair, Barber B. Conable, Jr.
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Two - Tape 4 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 82 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15439)
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Two - Tape 5 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 89 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15440)
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Two - Tape 6 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 71 minutes (plus 24 minutes of unrelated recording).; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15441)
      The meeting recording is found on the first 71 minutes of tape. The rest of the tape contains rock music.
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Three - Tape 9 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 90 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15444)
      Session chair, Peter G. Peterson (Council of Foreign Relations).
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Three - Tape 10 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 73 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15445)
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Four - Tape 7 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 90 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15442)
      Session chair, Ambassador Liu Shuqing. Session on the Future of the Sino-American Political Relationship.
    - Seventh United States-China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center, Session Four - Tape 8 of 10, 1994 October 8-10; 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15443)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 1 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15583A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 1 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15583B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 2 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 57 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15584B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 2 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 57 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15584A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 3 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15585A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 3 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15585B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 4 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15586A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 4 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15586B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 5 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15587A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 5 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15587B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 6 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15588A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 6 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15588B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 7 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15589A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 7 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15589B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 8 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15590A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 8 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15590B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 9 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15591A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 9 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15591B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 10 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15592A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 10 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15592B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 11 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 57 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15593A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 11 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 57 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15593B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 12 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15594A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 12 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15594B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 13 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15595A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 13 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15595B)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (English Language) - Tape 14 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 53 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15596A)
    - Eighth United States - China Dialogue, Beijing (Chinese Language) - Tape 14 of 14, 1996 June 22-30; Sound, 53 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15596B)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 1 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 89 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15504)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 2 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 91 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15505)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 3 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 89 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15506)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 4 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 64 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15507)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 5 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 90 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15508)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 6 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 93 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15509)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 7 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 87 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15510)
    - Ninth United States - China Dialogue, Pocantico Conference Center - Tape 8 of 9, 1997 December 12-15; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15511)